Guide to the Apple Computer, Inc. Records M1007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Audiovisual materials, Series 14
  - Apple Library Cataloged videotapes, Subseries 14.8
    - Apple business learning: ahead of the game [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/703/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (9:08 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 84, Videotape 1)
      Multimedia -- Business applications; HyperCard; Macintosh -- Success stories; Apple Computer, Inc.; Sculley, John
    - HyperCard for interactive video [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1987; VT/931/1987; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. + 2 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 84, Videotape 2)
      HyperCard -- Independent study; Interactive video -- HyperCard; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Apple's commitment: higher education [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1986; VT/1030/1986; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic) (5:09 min.): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 84, Videotape 3)
      Macintosh -- Higher education; Executive speeches -- Sculley, John; Apple Computer, Inc.
  - Audiocassettes, Subseries 14.9
    - The Apple boogie. -- Cupertino: Apple Computer, Inc., 1982 - 1987; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 1)
    - Apple "Elvis" segment, undated; 1 sound cassette: Dolby B (Box 87, Audiocassettes 2)
    - Apple II forever, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 3)
    - Apple news from the Louisiana territory, 1991; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 4)
    - Building quality into software / Tom DeMarco, 1989 Dec. 7; 1 sound cassette (90 min.) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 5)
    - Fall 1990 new products: Macintosh II, LC, Classic, Macintosh 12" RGB & Macintosh 12" mono displays. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 6)
    - Forever. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1990; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 7)
    - French vision. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1984 Nov. 27; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 8)
    - A guided tour of MacDraw. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 9)
    - A guided tour of MacWrite-MacPaint. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., undated; 1 sound cassette (cy 1) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 10)
    - A guided tour of MacWrite-MacPaint. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., undated; 1 sound cassette (cy 2) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 11)
    - The Macintosh family: positioning and information. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1989 Mar.; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 12)
    - Introduction: Macintosh IIci competitive information & Macintosh portable competitive information. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 13)
    - Large business radio. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1992 Apr.; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 14)
      Vital: what it means for you and your customer
    - Large business radio. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1992 June; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 15)
      Strategic alliance update
    - Macintosh plus: a guided tour. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1986; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 16)
    - Macintosh vs. Windows. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1990 Sept.; 1 sound cassette (cy 1) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 17)
    - Macintosh vs. Windows. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1990 Sept.; 1 sound cassette (cy 2) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 18)
    - Market intelligence update: competitive response. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1989 Sept. 19; 1 sound cassette (30 min.) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 19)
    - Market intelligence update. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1990 Feb.; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 20)
    - Market intelligence update. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1990 May; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 21)
    - Market intelligence update. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1991 Mar.; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 22)
    - Market intelligence update. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1991 Apr.; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 23)
    - Market intelligence update. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1991 May; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 24)
    - Market intelligence update. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1991 June; 1 sound cassette (cy 1) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 25)
    - Market intelligence update. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1991 June; 1 sound cassette (cy 2) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 26)
    - Market intelligence update. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1992 Apr.; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 27)
    - Market intelligence update. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1992 May; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 28)
    - Market intelligence update. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1992 July; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 29)
    - Market intelligence update. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1992 Aug.; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 30)
    - Marketing breakfast - international. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1983 July 14; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 31)
    - Marketing breakfast - international. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1983 July 14; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 32)
    - Middle managers. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1986 June 23; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 33)
    - North Pacific newstape: a quarterly summary of North Pacific Area news. -- Palo Alto, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1987; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 34)
    - Product training Macintosh family positioning: featuring Macintosh IIci and Macintosh portable. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1989 Sept.; 1 sound cassette (Box 87, Audiocassettes 35)
    - Radio Apple, Vol. 1.: The competitive value of diversity. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1987 Sept.; 1 sound cassette (19:25 min.) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 36)
    - Radio Apple, Vol. 2: Exceptional growth. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988 Aug.; 1 sound cassette (23:30 min.) (cy 1) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 37)
    - Radio Apple, Vol. 2: Exceptional growth. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988 Aug.; 1 sound cassette (23:30 min.) (cy 2) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 38)
    - Radio Apple. Special edition: Apple's Global Leader's meeting including New Enterprise. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988 Oct.; 1 sound cassette (27 min.) (cy 1) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 39)
    - Radio Apple. Special edition: Apple's Global Leader's meeting including New Enterprise. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988 Oct.; 1 sound cassette (27 min.) (cy 2) (Box 87, Audiocassettes 40)
    - 90WWDC-6 Thursday keynote: John Sculley. -- (Apple Worldwide Developer's Conference, 1990), 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 1)
    - Bay Area Council. Speaker: John Sculley / KQED-FM, 1987 Jan. 16; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 2)
    - Cincinnati dinner, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 3)
    - French Project journal. John Sculley, 1985 Feb. 16; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 4)
    - Interview Chris Wittle, Esquire Magazine, 1984 Oct. 11; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 5)
    - John Sculley interview, Geneve, 1984 Oct. 31; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 6)
    - John Sculley German speeches, Koln Apple expo, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 7)
    - GM project, 1985 Mar. 5; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 8)
    - Kay Holland interview: John Sculley, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 9)
    - John Sculley: Infocorp speech, 1984 Dec. 11; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 10)
    - Investors in the Air. The John Sculley interview, n.d. July - Aug.; 1 sound cassette (cy 1) (Box 88, Audiocassettes 11)
    - Investors in the Air. The John Sculley interview, n.d. July - Aug.; 1 sound cassette (cy 2) (Box 88, Audiocassettes 12)
    - John Sculley / WNBC, 1987 Oct. 29; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 13)
    - The Larry King show, no. 1, 1989 Oct. 14; 1 sound cassette (cy 1) (Box 88, Audiocassettes 14)
    - The Larry King show, no. 2, 1989 Oct. 14; 1 sound cassette (cy 1) (Box 88, Audiocassettes 15)
    - The Larry King show, no. 1, 1989 Oct. 14; 1 sound cassette (cy 2) (Box 88, Audiocassettes 16)
    - The Larry King show, no. 2, 1989 Oct. 14; 1 sound cassette (cy 2) (Box 88, Audiocassettes 17)
    - John Sculley presentation to MIT Sloan School, 1984 Sept. 26; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 18)
    - PCBA banquet, 1980 Jan. 29; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 19)
    - PBG - Palm Springs, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 20)
    - Philadelphia challenge, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 21)
    - John Sculley: Reflections. -- (Powersharing series, no. 164). -- Riverside, Conn.: Powersharing, Inc., 1987; 1 sound cassette (cy 1) (Box 88, Audiocassettes 22)
    - John Sculley: Reflections. -- (Powersharing series, no. 164). -- Riverside, Conn.: Powersharing, Inc., 1987; 1 sound cassette (cy 2) (Box 88, Audiocassettes 23)
    - John Sculley: sales meeting, Boca, 1986 Sept.; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 24)
    - John Sculley speech to Ad Age, Ad Week, Conrad Hilton, Chicago, 1979 Aug. 19; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 25)
    - John Sculley speech to sales force, 1979 Sept. 5; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 26)
    - Speech to SDO employees, Pepsi, Marion, Ill., 1979 Dec. 18; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 27)
    - Tomorrow's odyssey: what Apple has to do next / John Sculley, 1988; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 28)
    - John Sculley: Wharton graduate orientation, 1979 Sept. 4; 1 sound cassette (Box 88, Audiocassettes 29)
    - MacBug blues [kit] (copy 1), 1991; Kit 28; 1 sound cassette + 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. + 1 v. (Box 89, Audiocassettes 1)
    - MacBugs blues [kit] (copy 2), 1991; Kit 28; 1 sound cassette + 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. + 1 v. (Box 89, Audiocassettes 2)
    - The Apple boogie. -- Cupertino: Apple Computer, Inc., 1982 - 1987; 1 sound cassette (cy 2) (Box 92, Audiocassettes 1)
    - Apple Computer. -- Los Angeles: BBDO/West; dist. Multimedia Services, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 2)
      AP 2186 Speak for yourself (30 sec.) -- AP 2086 1812-A (30 sec.) -- AP 1986 Fall Back-A (30 sec.) -- AP 2586 Open House ver. A rev. (1 min.) -- AP 2787 Returns #1 (1 min.) -- AP 2788 Returns revisited (1 min.)
    - Apple Computer. Chicago. 6:00 p.m. I, 1983 May 2; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 3)
    - Apple Computer. Chicago. 6:00 p.m. III, 1983 May 2; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 4)
    - Apple Computer. Chicago. 8:00 p.m. I, 1983 May 2; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 5)
    - Apple Computer. Chicago. 8:00 p.m. III, 1983 May 2; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 6)
    - Apple Horizons. Education Sales seminar. Module 1: how to talk to your Apple, 1982; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 7)
    - Apple Horizons. Education Sales seminar. Module II: microcomputer applications, 1982; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 8)
    - Apple Horizons. Education Sales seminar. Module III: making software decisions, 1982; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 9)
    - Apple Horizons. Education Sales seminar. Module IV: selecting a personal computer, 1982; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 10)
    - Apple Horizons. Apple III: a beginning. Module 1: the Apple III system, 1982; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 11)
    - Apple Horizons. Apple III: a beginning. Module 2: applications software, 1982; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 12)
    - Apple Horizons. Apple III: a beginning. Module 3: working together - hardware and software, 1982; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 13)
    - Apple Horizons. Apple III: getting organized. Module 1: organizing & managing information, 1983; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 14)
    - Apple Horizons. Apple III: getting organized. Module 2: using peripheral devices, 1983; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 15)
    - Apple Horizons. Small business and professional practice seminar. Module 1: business needs and solutions, 1983; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 16)
    - Apple Horizons. Small business and professional practice seminar. Module 2: Apple IIe version Apple applications, 1983; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 17)
    - Apple Horizons. Small business and professional practice seminar. Module 2: Apple III version Apple applications, 1983; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 18)
    - Apple II forever, 1984; 1 sound cassette Master (Box 92, Audiocassettes 19)
    - Apple II forever, 1984; 1 sound cassette USE copy (Box 92, Audiocassettes 20)
    - DeMarco, Tom. Building quality into sfotware: uncut recording of a 12/7/89 presentation at Apple Computer, 1989 Dec. 7; 1 sound cassette (90 min.) (Box 92, Audiocassettes 21)
    - A guided tour of MacProject / Bob Loftis, 1984; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 22)
    - Impressions, undated; 1 sound cassette Master (Box 92, Audiocassettes 23)
      National account program -- K-12 education program -- University consortium program -- Value added reseller program
    - Impressions, undated; 1 sound cassette Use copy (Box 92, Audiocassettes 24)
    - Impressions, undated; 1 sound cassette Master (Box 92, Audiocassettes 25)
      Corporate strategy and overview -- Macintosh/LISA family -- Apple II family -- Datacommunications -- Service and support general -- Service and support for National account, K-12, and University -- Service and support for value added resellers
    - Impressions, undated; 1 sound cassette Use copy (Box 92, Audiocassettes 26)
    - Intelligent choices merchandise plan training materials. Desktop / Plan automatic demonstration, 1980; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 27)
    - Leading the way: Apple Computer, 1984; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 28)
    - The Macintosh family: positioning and information, 1989 Mar.; 1 sound cassette Master (Box 92, Audiocassettes 29)
    - The Macintosh family: positioning and information, 1989 Mar.; 1 sound cassette Use copy (Box 92, Audiocassettes 30)
    - Macintosh Plus: a guided tour, 1985; 1 sound cassette Master (Box 92, Audiocassettes 31)
    - Macintosh Plus: a guided tour, 1985; 1 sound cassette Use copy (Box 92, Audiocassettes 32)
    - New employee orientation: theme music, 1986 Jan.; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 33)
    - New product support engineer interviews, 1991 Oct.; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 34)
    - Profit sharing boogie, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 35)
    - San Diego 8340-01 Computer owners, 6:00 p.m., males & females, 1983 May 3; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 36)
    - San Diego 8340-01 Computer owners, 8:00 p.m., males & females, 1983 May 3; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 37)
    - Xerox. Apple institucional / ofertazo, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 38)
    - The Planning Forum conference - San Francisco. Chaos: a new ally?, 1985 May 22-25; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 39)
    - The Planning Forum conference - San Francisco. Front line strategic management: marketing success at Marriott, 1985 May 22-25; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Audiocassettes 40)
  - Reel-to-reel audiotapes, Subseries 14.10
    - John Sculley, Miami, 1973 Nov. 16; 1 sound tape reel (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - John Sculley PCBA banquet, 1980 Jan. 29; 1 sound tape reel (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Film reels, Subseries 14.11
    - Apple Computers / Chiat Day, undated; 1 reel of 1: sd., col.; 16 mm. (Box 89, Folder 5)
      1984 (1 min.) -- Skin Ritz
    - John Sculley presentation reel, undated; 1 reel of 1: sd., col.; 16 mm. (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 reel of 1: sd., col.; 16 mm. (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Chiat/Day. 1984, 1 reel of 1: sd., col.; 16 mm. (Box 93, Folder 3)
      1984 -- Making of 1984
  - VHS Masters, Subseries 14.12
    - Macintosh, 1983 Sept.; 81; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (10 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. Master (Box 90, Folder 1)
      Existence and Location of Copies note
      VHS use copy available: Series 14, Box 91, Videotape 1
    - Bluebusters [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1984; VT/95/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (4:14 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. Master (Box 90, Folder 2)
      VHS use copy available: Series 14, Box 91, Videotape 2
      IBM Macintosh; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - The Macintosh Office, 1985 Feb. 18; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (8:30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. Master (Box 90, Folder 3)
      VHS use copy available: Series 14, Box 91, Videotape 3
    - Early reactions to the Macintosh, 1985 Jan. 18; 116; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (3:40 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. Master (Box 90, Folder 4)
      VHS use copy available: Series 14, Box 91, Videotape 4
    - Macintosh year in review [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1985 Mar. 17; 1 videocassette of 1 (3:06 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. Master (Box 90, Folder 5)
      VHS use copy available: Series 14, Box 91, Videotape 5
    - Marketing research: Macintosh, 1985 Mar. 28; 53; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (24:35 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. Master (Box 90, Folder 6)
      VHS use copy available: Series 14, Box 91, Videotape 6
    - McKenna, Regis. TV pitch, 1984 Apr. 11; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (7:10 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. Master (Box 90, Folder 7)
      VHS use copy available: Series 14, Box 91, Videotape 7
    - Macintosh public relations: video news clips, 1985 Feb. 18; 47; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (28 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. Master (Box 90, Folder 8)
      VHS use copy available: Series 14, Box 91, Videotape 8
  - VHS Use copies, Subseries 14.13
    - Macintosh, 1983 Sept.; 81; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (10 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. use copy (Box 91, Folder 1)
      U-matic original: Series 14, Box 22, Videotape 4
    - Bluebusters [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1984; VT/95/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (4:14 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. use copy (Box 91, Folder 2)
      U-matic original: Series 14, Box 83, Videotape 1
    - The Macintosh Office, 1985 Feb. 18; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (8:30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. use copy (Box 91, Folder 3)
      U-matic original: Series 14, Box 22, Videotape 5
    - Early reactions to the Macintosh, 1985 Jan. 18; 116; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (3:40 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. use copy (Box 91, Folder 4)
      U-matic original: Series 14, Box 21, Videotape 2
    - Macintosh year in review [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1985 Mar. 17; 1 videocassette of 1 (3:06 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. use copy (Box 91, Folder 5)
      U-matic original: Series 14, Box 84, Videotape 4
    - Marketing research: Macintosh, 1985 Mar. 28; 53; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (24:35 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. use copy (Box 91, Folder 6)
      U-matic original: Series 14, Box 23, Videotape 1
    - McKenna, Regis. TV pitch, 1984 Apr. 11; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (7:10 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. use copy (Box 91, Folder 7)
      U-matic original: Series 14, Box 25, Videotape 3
    - Macintosh public relations: video news clips, 1985 Feb. 18; 47; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (28 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. use copy (Box 91, Folder 8)
      U-matic original: Series 14, Box 22, Videotape 6
- Digital media, Series 15
  Access to the digital files on either 3.5 or 5.25 in. floppy diskettes requires at least 2 weeks advance notice to allow staff to have use copies made.
  - Computer diskettes, Subseries 15.1
    - AppleLink 6.0. Program disk 1, 1987-1990; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 1)
    - AppleLink 6.0. Program disk 2, 1987-1990; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 2)
    - Apple earthquake preparedness stack / Apple Computer, Inc. Corporate Environmental Health & Safety, undated; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 3)
    - Apple IIc plus art, undated; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 4)
    - Apple IIe plus art, undated; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 5)
    - Apple IIgs and System software 5.0, 1989; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 6)
    - Apple IIgs (APW) programmer's workshop. -- Ver. 1.0B1, 1986 Oct. 31; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 7)
    - Apple IIgs art, undated; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 8)
    - Apple IIgs CD setup, 1988; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 9)
    - Apple IIgs educational demo. -- V. 1.0, 1986 Oct. 13; 66; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 10)
    - Apple IIgs educational demo. -- V. 1.0, 1986 Oct. 13; 66; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 11)
    - Apple IIgs note synthesizer. -- V. 1.0, 1986 Oct. 20; 74; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 12)
    - AppleTalk update disk. -- Ver. 1.0, 1987 Feb. 20; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 13)
    - Becks Macintosh system tools. -- Ver. 2.0B1, 1987 Feb. 19; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 14)
    - Becks Macintosh utilities. -- Ver. 2.0B1, 1987 Feb. 19; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 15)
    - Desktop publishing participant's disk: introduction to Macintosh, 1987; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 16)
    - Ethertalk installer. -- Ver. 2.0.1, 1989 Sept. 12; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 17)
    - Guided tour of MacDraw. -- Ver. 1.1, 1986 Mar. 24; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 18)
    - Guided tour of Macintosh 512K enhanced. -- Ver. 1.0, 1986 Mar. 24; PN:690-5090 REV A; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (cy 1) (Box 1, Diskette 19)
    - Guided tour of Macintosh 512K enhanced. -- Ver. 1.0, 1986 Mar. 24; PN:690-5090 REV A; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (cy 2) (Box 1, Diskette 20)
    - HD 20SC installation. -- Ver. 1.0, 1986 Aug. 28; 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 21)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0B51, 1986, 1987; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 2); 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 22)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0B51, 1986, 1987; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 3); 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 23)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0B51, 1986, 1987; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 4); 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 24)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0B6, 1987 June 17; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 1); 3.5 in. (cy 1) (Box 1, Diskette 25)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0B6, 1987 June 17; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 2); 3.5 in. (cy 1) (Box 1, Diskette 26)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0B6, 1987 June 17; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 3); 3.5 in. (cy 1) (Box 1, Diskette 27)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0B6, 1987 June 17; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 4); 3.5 in. (cy 1) (Box 1, Diskette 28)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0B6, 1987 June 17; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 1); 3.5 in. (cy 2) (Box 1, Diskette 29)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0B6, 1987 June 17; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 2); 3.5 in. (cy 2) (Box 1, Diskette 30)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0B6, 1987 June 17; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 3); 3.5 in. (cy 2) (Box 1, Diskette 31)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0B6, 1987 June 17; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 4); 3.5 in. (cy 2) (Box 1, Diskette 32)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0, 1987 July 27; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 2); 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 33)
    - Macintosh Hypercard. -- Ver. 1.0, 1987 July 27; 1 computer diskette of 4 (disk 3); 3.5 in. (Box 1, Diskette 34)